afromix.org 2015-01-28

# Privacy Statement

## Information Collection and Use

Afromix.org is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.  
Afromix.org collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

### Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to security@afromix.org
